Automobile, Steel, IT, Coffee, and Energy are some of the Tata Group's
brands that have carved
a special place in the hearts of every Indian. Today, we'll
talk about their insurance vertical, Tata
AG Insurance.
Basically, coverage is available for everything from surgery to dental, OT,
maternity, and global coverage.
Researching your own medical
condition online takes about a few hours.
Automobile, Steel, IT, Coffee, and Energy are
some of the Tata Group's brands that have carved
a special place in the hearts of every Indian.
Friends, Tata is the only domestic brand
that every Indian is proud of.
Today, we'll talk about their insurance vertical,
Tata AG Insurance. If
you're searching for a medical plan, is
their
insurance right for you?
If you trust the Tata brand,
you can consider this plan. This
plan basically covers everything from basic surgery to
dental,
OPTD, and global coverage. So,
if you require these features,
you can consider this plan. Friends,
if you want to purchase comprehensive health insurance
for yourself,  If you are a health advisor,
researching on the internet or reading their terms and conditions takes
approximately five to seven hours.
If you want to purchase a good
health insurance smoothly, you can contact our
IIDA registered insurance advisor
who will research the market and provide you with the
best health
insurance and customized health insurance for you and your family,
free of cost. You
can review your health insurance
so that you can purchase the best health insurance for yourself.
You can contact us on the number.
If you
want to be successful in a health insurance career and
want to serve people, you will be
happy to know that we recruit
insurance advisors for insurance companies on an all-India basis.
We provide them with the
best
training and motivation
and are running
a great
insurance business today by serving the best people in the market. So
if you want to do the same,
contact us. Our team will help you and
we will work together to take you forward.  I have been
associated with the insurance industry for 15 years.
We have trained and motivated many agents
who are currently
doing very well in the market.
Friends, let us look at and
review the plans in detail. Before that, I
request you that if you have not yet subscribed to the channel, then do so so that
in the future
you will keep getting such latest information on this channel. Please press the bell icon.
Friends, first of all, if
we have to search any insurance plan, then
what do we look at? Claim
Settlement Ratio. Right, which company has the
best claim settlement ratio? If we
talk about the claim settlement ratio of Tata AIG company,
what is the average 3-year claim settlement ratio from 2021
to 24? Right, that of Tata is
at 96. If we compare it, then
Cair's is at 90, HDFC's is at 98
and Aditya Bala Capital's is at 95. So,
if you compare it, then almost all of them are
correct.  A good claim settlement ratio is considered,
right after that comes the network hospital,
right whose network hospital is how high
because if you
get a network hospital near your house, then you get the
facility of cashless smoothly very easily,
right so if we talk about network hospital,
here we will see that the
network hospital of TA is 10000 comparatively, if
we see that of ADFC Ergo is 11500, that of Care
Health Insurance is 16000 and if we
talk about Aditya Bila Capital, their
network hospital is 11000, right here
also you can see a decent network hospital of
TA, now friends let us talk about
premium, if we talk about premium, if we talk about premium
of an adult, if we talk about premium of
30 years, if we talk about
Delhi, right talk about premium of Delhi, the
premium coming in Medicare plan is
₹11949, if we talk about
comparative other plans like Optimus Sikar,
if we see their comparative, Optimus  That
of Secure was
6759. If we talk about that of Care Supreme, it is
11547. If we talk about Toodle, the
premium in Medicare plan is
19118. The premium of Optimal Secure
is
24300. That of Care Supreme is 154.31. So if
we look at premium wise also, then
comparatively it seems a little cheaper
in medical plan. So friends, if
we talk about two adults and one child
in Medicare plan, then
basically the age of the child, if we consider
5 years, then the premium of Delhi Medicare
plan, if we talk about medical plan,
if we talk about premium, it is 22700. The
premium of Optimal Secure is
28765. If we
talk about Cash Supreme, the premium of Cash Supreme is
1968. So here also if we look at it, then
comparatively the premium is cheaper than them, but
you do not have to go cheap, you have to do more.  It
is important to see the features etc. because if you
skip the video after seeing it cheap,
you may also suffer a loss. So, in the future, we will
talk more about what things are not covered in these plans
and what things are capped so that
you do not face any problem in claiming in the future.
If we talk about room rent
restriction, then
what is room rent restriction? The Medicare product
variant comes with restriction of shared
room. So, if you take this variant of Medicare product, then
you will get shared room in it
while other variants like Medicare
and Medicare Premium have no room rent
restrictions. So, if you
take Medicare Premier or Medicare plan, then there are no
room rent
restrictions in it. Friends, now let's talk about
global coverage.
If we talk about global coverage, then the Medicare Premium
variant gives you global coverage
for conditions diagnosed
in India up to the same shot. If you get
diagnosed with any disease in India, then
you can go abroad and get global coverage i.e.
global treatment.  Right
next we talk about maternity cover
right so the Medicare Premier plan
basically gives you maternity coverage in it so
if your sum assured is 50 lakhs
right then the sum assured is up to 50 lakhs
in the sum assured you will get 50 lakhs for boy child and 60 lakhs
for girl child that is you will get up to 50
lakhs in the sum assured you will get up to 50000
for boy child and
60000 for girl child you get an
amount of 60000 as maternity benefit if
we talk about 75 lakhs and above sum assured if it is
basically 1 lakh for
boy child and 1.2 lakh for girl child right so
this is also a maternity cover which you can consider if
you want this benefit then
you can consider this plan friends if we talk about the initial waiting
period then in this plan
basically the waiting period is 30 days which normally everyone
in the insurance company  There is an initial
waiting period of 30 days. Talking about PD,
basically Medicare Premier has a
PD of two years, which means pre-
assisting disease waiting period.
If we look at Medicare, it is of 3 years
and if we take Medicare Protect plan, then in
which there is a pre-assisting
waiting period of 4 years. Right,
if we talk about specific illness waiting period, in
which all the plans have a
specific illness of two years, like cataract,
hernia, stone, piles or any
planning surgery, basically their
waiting period is 2 years. Right, friends, now let
us talk about the copayment of features.
Basically, there is
no copayment in Medicare Premier. There is no copayment in Medicare also.
If you
choose a Medicare product plan in
which % if higher category of room is
opted for, then do
you get sharing room in the medical product plan if you have opted for a
higher category room?  If you take it, then
you will have to pay a copayment of 10, that is,
your copayment will be 10, which you will have to
pay extra. Talking about room rent,
in Medicare premium there is any room,
in Medicare there is any room, which I have already talked about,
in Medicare product you will get a
shared room. Talking about pre and post hospital
coverage, right in Medical Premier there will be
60 and 60 and 90 days pre
hospitalization, 60 days and post
hospitalization in which there will be 90 days,
60 and 200 days for same SOD 75 lakhs
and now if your same SOD is above 75 lakhs, then
you get a pre post hospitalization cover of 60 and 200 days,
right
in Medicare it is 60 and 90 days, if we
talk about Medicare product, in which you have a
pre and post hospitalization cover of 30 and 60 days.
Talking about no-cost bonus, friends, you will get
50 percent in medical premium and up
to the  100% off the sum shot in Medicare which
is 50 per up to the 100% off the sum shot will increase by 50-50 every time.
If we talk about Medicare product in which it will increase by 10 per 10 and the maximum will
reach 100%, that is,
by doing 10 per 10, the maximum will reach 100%.
So this was copayment, room
rent and duplicate bonus. Ok, now let's move on to coverage.
How much coverage do you get
in Medical Premier Plan? You get coverage of Rs.
5 lakh to 10 lakh, 15 lakh, 20 lakh, 25 lakh, 50 lakh, 75 lakh,
1 crore, 2 crore and 3
crore. You can take sum shot
in Medical Premier Plan.
Your coverage starts in Medicare Plan, that is, it
starts from Rs. 3 lakh, 3 lakh, 4 lakh, 5 lakh, 7.5 lakh,
10 lakh, 15 lakh and 20 lakh.
If you want to take medical product variant in
which your sum shot starts from Rs. 2 lakh.
You can take a sum assured of Rs 2 lakh, 3 lakh, 4 lakh and 5 lakh. Friends, in this plan
you can also take dental OBT coverage.
If you take the Medicare Premier
variant, it gives coverage for dental treatment. The
Medicare
Premier plan
provides dental treatment, like root canal
treatment, single and multiple stitching, single or
multiple. You can take root treatment, tooth
extraction, la and filling, taken on OPD
basis up to the specific limits, right
between 10k and 25k, based on the cover
amount taken.
You can claim from Rs 10,000 to Rs 25,000 depending on the cover amount.
In which you get dental OBT coverage.
If you take Medicare Premier, but you
take Medicare Premium, you
also get dental OPD cover. Right, friends, this
was the Medicare plan of the TAAG company. So,
how did you like the Medicare plan? Right, there are
some benefits in it, like if we
compare it with other plans,
you might  The benefits may seem a little less, but
if your needs are being fulfilled and
you trust the brand, then
you can consider this plan.
If you want to compare this plan with theirs, then
some of the features in Nibha Bappa's Aspire plan are there,
which you can compare with this plan.
After that, if you have a Care Health
Insurance plan,
you can compare it with Care Ultimate Care Plan as well. By
comparing,
you can take the best decision. But if you are
confused about health insurance, doing research and finding the
best health insurance for you is a
very difficult task in today's date. So,
if you
want to purchase the best health insurance for yourself,
then our team is basically an IRD
registered team which will provide you guidance
free of cost. So,
if you face any such problem, God forbid, then
you do
not need to go to any hospital and make rounds of the hospital.
We recruit insurance agents on an all India level basis and
train them.  We
motivate and do the best work in the market,
serve the people.
In today's date, if you
want to be successful in insurance career, then
contact us.
We recruit advisors for insurance companies on all India level basis. See you
in the next video with the next and new topic. Till then, bye bye,
Jai Hind,
Vande Mataram.